grade_8_part_1 = {
    "Repeating decimals": [
        {
            "Repeating decimals": {
            "Definition": "Repeating decimals are when a pattern of numbers repeats over and over after the decimal point.",
            "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "What is the decimal that is equivalent to 2/3?",
                        "Answer": "Repeatedly divide 2 by 3, we get the number 0.\overline(6).",
                        "Type": "Narrative",
                        "Difficulty": 3
                    }
                ],
            "Rate": 1,
            }
        },
        {
            "Square roots and cube roots": {
            "Definition": "The square root of a number is the factor that we can multiply by itself to get that number. The cube root of a number is the factor that we multiply by itself three times to get that number.",
            "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "Alex has a cube box with volume 64 cm^3.\nWhat is the side length of that cube box?",
                        "Answer": "We need to find the cube root of 64.\nSince \sqrt{3}{64} = 4, the side length of the cube box is 4 cm.",
                        "Type": "Narrative",
                        "Difficulty": 3
                    }
                ],
            "Rate": 1,
            }
        },
        {
            "Irrational numbers": {
            "Definition": "Irrational numbers are numbers that cannot be expressed as a fraction of two integers.",
            "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "Luke has a square piece of paper with area 5.\nIs the side length of this paper a rational or irrational number?",
                        "Answer": "The side length of this paper is \sqrt(5), which is an irrational number.",
                        "Type": "Narrative",
                        "Difficulty": 3
                    }
                ],
            "Rate": 1,   
            }
        },
        {
            "Exponent properties":{
            "Definition": "Exponent properties are rules that we can use to simplify expressions that contain exponents, which include: Product rule, Power rule, Quotient rule, Zero exponent rule.",
            "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "Compare (2^10)/(2^4) and 3^2^2.",
                        "Answer": "We will calculate both quantities.\nAbout A = (2^10)/(2^4), applying the quotient rule, we get A = 2^(10-4) = 2^6 = 64.\nAbout B = 3^2^2, it is equal to 3^4 = 81.\nSince 81 > 64, we get B > A.",
                        "Type": "Narrative",
                        "Difficulty": 3
                    }
                ],
            "Rate": 1,   
            }
        },
        {
            "Scientific notation":{
            "Definition": "Scientific notation is a way of writing really big or really small numbers in a way that makes them easier to work with. For example, 0.000000000005 is hard to read, but when we put it in scientific notation, we get 5 * 10^(-12).",
            "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "A color photograph taken with a digital camera is converted into digital format using 4 * 10^0 bytes per pixel. Photographs taken with the camera each have 2.2 * 10^6 pixels. How many bytes are there in one photo? Write your answer in scientific notation.",
                        "Answer": "To find out how many bytes in one photo we can multiply: bytes per photograph = pixels in photograph * bytes per pixel = (2.2 * 10^6) * (4 * 10^0).\nWe can separate this formula into: (2.2 * 4) * (10^6 * 10^0) = 8.8 * 10^6.\nSo there are 8.8 * 10^6 bytes in one photo.",
                        "Type": "Narrative",
                        "Difficulty": 3
                    }
                ],
            "Rate": 1,   
            }
        }
    ],
    "Solving equations with one unknown":[
        {
            "Equations with variables on both sides":{
            "Definition": "In an equation with variables on both sides, the unknown quantity (usually represented by a letter such as x) appears on both the left and right sides of the equation. To solve this type of equation, we usually try to isolate the variable on one side by manipulating the equation until we have only one instance of the variable.",
            "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "Solve for c in the following equation: 6c + 14 = −5c + 4 + 9c",
                        "Answer": "First we combine the like term: 6c + 14 = 4c + 4.\nThen we subtract 4c from each side: 2c + 14 = 4.\nThen we subtract 14 from each side: 2c = -10.\nFinally, we obtain c = -5.",
                        "Type": "Narrative",
                        "Difficulty": 3
                    }
                ],
            "Rate": 1,   
            }
        },
        {
            "Equations with parentheses":{
            "Definition": "Parentheses can be used in equations to group terms together. To solve an equation that contains parentheses, we usually use the distributive property to simplify the equation.",
            "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "Solve for g in this equation: 6(−2g−1) = −(13g+2)",
                        "Answer": "First we use the distribute property: -12g - 6 = -13g - 2.\nThen we add 13g to each side, as well as add 6 to each side:-12g - 6 + 13g + 6 = -13g - 2 + 13g + 6.\nThe equation is then equivalent to: g = 4.\nSo the answer is g = 4.",
                        "Type": "Narrative",
                        "Difficulty": 3
                    }
                ],
            "Rate": 1,   
            }
        },
        {
            "Equations word problems":{
            "Definition": "When it comes to word problems, we usually have to take a few extra steps to set up the equation before we can solve it. We start by identifying the unknown quantity and assigning it a variable. Then we translate the problem into an equation, using the information given in the word problem. Once we have the equation, we solve it as we would any other equation.",
            "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "The sum of 6 consecutive integers is 519. What is the third number in this sequence?",
                        "Answer": "Call the first number in the sequence x.\nThe sum of the 6 consecutive integers is: x + (x+1) + (x+2) + (x+3) + (x+4) + (x+5) = 519.\nCombining the like terms, we have: 6x + 15 = 519.\nSolving the equation, we obtain: x = (519 - 15) / 6 = 84.\nSo the third number in the sequence is: x+2 = 86.",
                        "Type": "Narrative",
                        "Difficulty": 3
                    }
                ],
            "Rate": 1,   
            }
        }
    ],
    "Linear equation and functions":[
        {
            "Rates and proportional relationships":{
            "Definition": "A proportional relationship is when two quantities change so that they maintain a constant ratio to one another.",
            "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "The American antelope (pronghorn) and the wildebeest are among the fastest mammals on the planet, particularly at running long distances. The maximum recorded speed for the antelope is 88.5km/h, which it can sustain for nearly one kilometer. On the other hand, the distance, d, in kilometers that the wildebeest can run in t hours is given by the equation d = 80.5t. Assuming both animals are running at constant speeds, which animal can run faster?",
                        "Answer": "The speed for the wildebeest is the distance the wildebeest can run in 1 hour. Since the distance is given by the equation d = 80.5td, for t = 1 hour we get: d = 80.5 km.\nSo the wildebeest's speed is 80.5 km/h, whereas the speed of the Amercian antelope is 88.5 km/h.\nSo the Amercian antelope can run faster.",
                        "Type": "Narrative",
                        "Difficulty": 3
                    }
                ],
            "Rate": 1,   
            }
        },
        {
            "Solutions to linear equations":{
            "Definition": "Solutions to linear equations are the x and y values that make the equation true.",
            "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "Give 3 ordered pairs that are solutions of the equation: 3x - y = 13.",
                        "Answer": "By substituting x = 1, 2, 3, we obtained three ordered pairs: (1, -10), (2, -7), (3, -4).\nThe three ordered pairs given are the solutions of the equation.",
                        "Type": "Narrative",
                        "Difficulty": 3
                    }
                ],
            "Rate": 1,   
            }
        },
        {
            "Intercepts":{
            "Definition": "The x-intercept is the point where a line crosses the x-axis, and the y-intercept is the point where a line crosses the y-axis.",
            "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "Determine the intercepts of the line: 4x - 3y = 17.",
                        "Answer": "When x = 0, we obtain: -3y = 17, so y = -17/3.\nWhen y = 0, we obtain: 4x = 17, so x = 17/4.\nIn conclusion, the x-intercept is: (17/4, 0) and the y-intercept is: (0, -17/3).",
                        "Type": "Narrative",
                        "Difficulty": 3
                    }
                ],
            "Rate": 1,   
            }
        },
        {
            "Slope":{
            "Definition": "Slope is a measure of the steepness of a line. The formula for slope is: (\Delta y) / (\Delta x).",
            "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "What is the slope of the line through (−2, −6) and (2, 2)?",
                        "Answer": "The difference in y-coordinate is: \Delta y = (-6) - 2 = -8.\nThe difference in x-coordinate is: \Delta x = (-2) - 2 = -4.\nSo the slope is: (\Delta y) - (\Delta x) = (-8) / (-4) = 2.",
                        "Type": "Narrative",
                        "Difficulty": 3
                    }
                ],
            "Rate": 1,   
            }
        },
        {
            "Slope-intercept form":{
            "Definition": "Slope-intercept form: y = mx + b.\nThe slope is m.\nThe y-coordinate of the y-intercept is b.",
            "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "Complete the equation of the line through (−9, −9) and (−6, 0).",
                        "Answer": "The slope of the line would be: (0 - (-9)) / (-6 - (-9)) = 9 / 3 = 3.\nThe formula of the line would be then: y = 3x + b.\nBy substituting x = -6, y = 0, we obtain b = 18.\nSo the formula of the line is: y = 3x + 18.",
                        "Type": "Narrative",
                        "Difficulty": 3
                    }
                ],
            "Rate": 1,   
            }
        },
        {
            "Function":{
            "Definition": "A function is a mathematical rule that matches inputs to outputs. We can think of it like a machine: put a number in, the machine does some calculations, and out pops a corresponding number.",
            "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "Find the output, d, when the input, t, is 11: d = t^2 −20 + 11t",
                        "Answer": "By substituting t = 11, we obtain t^2 = 121 and 11t = 121.\nSo d = 121 - 20 + 121 = 222.",
                        "Type": "Narrative",
                        "Difficulty": 3
                    }
                ],
            "Rate": 1,   
            }
        },
        {
            "Linear function":{
            "Definition": "A linear function is a type of function that produces a straight line when graphed. It follows the form y = mx + b, where m is the slope and b is the y-intercept.",
            "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "A young sumo wrestler goes on a special diet to gain weight. The variable w models the wrestler's weight (in kilograms) after the wrestler has been on a special diet for t months: w = 80 + 5.4t. How much weight does the wrestler gain every 2 months?",
                        "Answer": "Each month, the wrestler gains 5.4 kg, which is the slope of the linear function.\nSo every 2 months, the wrestler would gain: 5.4 * 2 = 10.8 kg.",
                        "Type": "Narrative",
                        "Difficulty": 3
                    }
                ],
            "Rate": 1,   
            }
        },
        {
            "Comparing linear functions":{
            "Definition": "We can compare two linear functions by looking at their slopes and y-intercepts. If the slopes are the same, the lines are parallel. If the slopes are different, the lines will intersect at some point. We can also compare the y-intercepts to determine where the lines cross the y-axis.",
            "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "Thor and Zeus strike with their hammers. The higher they raise their hammers before they strike, the louder the sound of the strike.\nThe following equation gives the loudness of Thor's strike (in decibels) as a function of the height from which he strikes (in centimeters): S = 3h + 25.\nThe line representing the equation of the loudness of Zeus' strike goes through 2 points: (15, 60) and (25, 90).\nWhose strike is louder when he strikes from a height of 40 centimeters?",
                        "Answer": "The slope of Zeus' equation is: (90 - 60) / (25 - 15) = 3.\nSo Zeus' equation has the form: S = 3h + b.\nBy substituting S = 90, h = 25, we obtain b = 15.\nSo the equation that gives the loudness of Zeus' strike is: S = 3h + 15.\nSince 25 > 15, we see that Thor's strike is always louder, which means that it is louder when he strikes from a height of 40 centimeters.",
                        "Type": "Narrative",
                        "Difficulty": 3
                    }
                ],
            "Rate": 1,   
            }
        },
        {
            "Constructing linear models for real-world relationships":{
            "Definition": "To construct a linear model, we need to determine the slope and y-intercept of the relationship. We can use two data points to find the slope, and then use one of the data points to solve for the y-intercept.",
            "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "Dominik uses 20 grams of filling for each dumpling he makes. He has 1500 grams of dumpling filling. The grams F of filling remaining is a function of d, the number of dumplings Dominik makes. Write the function's formula.",
                        "Answer": "When d = 0, F = 1500 and when d = 1, F = 1480.\nThe slope is then: (1500 - 1480) / (0 - 1) = -20.\nThe y-intercept is 1500.\nSo the function's formula is: F = 1500 - 20d.",
                        "Type": "Narrative",
                        "Difficulty": 3
                    }
                ],
            "Rate": 1,   
            }
        }
    ]
}

grade_8_part_2 = {
    "Systems of equation": [
        {
            "Intro to systems of equations":{
            "Definition": "A system of equations is a set of two or more equations that all use the same variables. We can try to solve the system by finding values for the variables that make all of the equations true at the same time.",
            "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "Given the following system of equations:\ny = -4x + 6,\n3x + 4y = -2.\nIs (2, 2) a solution of the system?",
                        "Answer": "Substituting x = 2, y = 2 to the first equation, we have: 2 = -4 * 2 + 6 = -2, which is a contradiction.\nSo (2, 2) is not a solution of the system.",
                        "Type": "Narrative",
                        "Difficulty": 3
                    }
                ],
            "Rate": 1,   
            }
        },
        {
            "Solving systems with substitution":{
            "Definition": "The substitution method is a technique for solving systems of linear equations. With substitution, we isolate one of the variables in one of the equations and then substitute that variable into the other equation.",
            "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "Solve the following system of equations:\n3x + y = -3,\nx = -y + 3.",
                        "Answer": "We can substitute x = -y + 3 into the first equation and get: 3(-y + 3) + y = -3 \Rightarrow -3y + 9 + y = -3 \Rightarrow -2y = -12 \Rightarrow y = 6.\nNow we get y = 6, we can obtain x = -y + 3 = -6 + 3 = -3.\nSo the solution for the system of equations is (-3, 6).",
                        "Type": "Narrative",
                        "Difficulty": 3
                    }
                ],
            "Rate": 1,   
            }
        },
        {
            "Systems of equations word problems":{
            "Definition": "Systems of equations can be used to model lots of different situations. For example, if we're trying to figure out how many adult and child tickets were sold at a movie theater, we might set up a system of equations with one equation for the total number of tickets and another equation for the total amount of money collected. We could also use systems of equations to model things like mixtures of solutions, distances and speeds of moving objects, or costs and quantities of different items.",
            "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "Ishaan is 2 times as old as Christopher. 35 years ago, Ishaan was 7 times as old as Christopher. How old is Ishaan now?",
                        "Answer": "Let the age of Ishaan be x years old, and the age of Christopher be y years old.\nIshaan is 2 times as old as Christopher, so x = 2y.\n35 years ago, Ishaan was 7 times as old as Christopher, so x - 35 = 7(y - 35).\nBy substituting x = 2y into the second equation, we obtain: 2y - 35 = 7(y - 35) \Rightarrow 2y - 35 = 7y - 245 \Rightarrow 5y = 210 \Rightarrow y = 42.\nSo Ishaan is 2 * 42 = 84 years old.",
                        "Type": "Narrative",
                        "Difficulty": 3
                    }
                ],
            "Rate": 1,   
            }
        },
    ],
    "Geometry": [
        {
            "Angles between intersecting lines":{
            "Definition": "When two lines intersect, they form angles with each other. Different types of angles have different relationships to one another. For example, vertical angles always have equal measures, while supplementary angles have measures that add up to 180 degrees.",
            "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "Given \angle LON is a straight angle. We also have \angle MON = 3x + 89 and \angle LOM = 8x + 58. Find \angle MON.",
                        "Answer": "Since \angle LON is a straight angle, we see that \angle MON and \angle LOM are two supplementary angles, and they sum up to 180 degrees.\nWe have the following equation: (3x + 89) + (8x + 58) = 180.\nSolving the equation, we obtain: 11x + 147 = 180 \Rightarrow 11x = 33 \Rightarrow x = 3.\nSo \angle MON = 3x + 89 = 98 degrees.",
                        "Type": "Narrative",
                        "Difficulty": 3
                    }
                ],
            "Rate": 1,   
            }
        },
        {
            "Triangle angles":{
            "Definition": "The sum of the measures of the three interior angles in a triangle is always 180 degrees. So, if we know two of the angle measures, we can use that information to find the measure of the third angle.",
            "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "Find the value of x in the triangle shown in the figure below.\nBEGIN PLOT:\nDraw(Acute triangle ABC)\nLabel(\angle ABC, 50 \degree)\nLabel(\angle BAC, 41 \degree)\nLabel(\angle ACB, x \degree)\nEND PLOT.",
                        "Answer": "We see that the sum of inner angles of a triangle is 180 \degree.\nSo we have: \angle ABC + \angle ACB + \angle BAC = 180 \degree.\nSo: 50 + 41 + x = 180.\nWhich means that x = 89.",
                        "Type": "Narrative",
                        "Difficulty": 3
                    }
                ],
            "Rate": 1,   
            }
        },
        {
            "Pythagorean theorem":{
            "Definition": "The Pythagorean theorem states that in a right triangle, the square of the hypotenuse is equal to the sum of the squares of the two other sides. It's often written as the equation a^2 + b^2 = c^2.",
            "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "Find the value of x in the triangle shown in the following figure.\nBEGIN PLOT:\nDraw(Right triangle ABC at A)\nLabel(Length of AB, x)\nLabel(Length of AC, 9)\nLabel(Length of BC, 15)\nEND PLOT.",
                        "Answer": "By the Pythagoras theorem, since the triangle ABC is has a right angle at A, we have: AB^2 + AC^2 = BC^2.\nSo: x^2 + 9^2 = 15^2.\nWhich means: x^2 = 225 - 81 = 144.\nSo x = 12.",
                        "Type": "Narrative",
                        "Difficulty": 3
                    }
                ],
            "Rate": 1,   
            }
        },
        {
            "Pythagorean theorem and distance between points":{
            "Definition": "We can draw a right triangle between the two points, and then use the Pythagorean theorem to find the hypotenuse, which is the distance we're looking for. The formula gives the distance between two points (x_1, y_1) and (x_2, y_2) on the coordinate plane is: \sqrt((x_1 - x_2)^2 - (y_1 - y_2)^2).",
            "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "Given 2 points A and B below:\nBEGIN PLOT:\nDraw('A', (5, 3))\nDraw('B', (7, 4))\nEND PLOT.\nDraw a point C above B (such that BC is perpendicular to the x axis) and has distance from B being BC = 5 units.\nWhat is the distance between A and C?",
                        "Answer": "The coordinate of point C is: (7, 4+5) or (7, 9).\nBy applying the formula for distance between 2 points on the coordinate plane, we have: AC = \sqrt((7-5)^2 + (9-3)^2) = \sqrt(2^2 + 6^2) = \sqrt(40).\nSimplifying it, we get the distance between A and C is 2\sqrt(10) units.",
                        "Type": "Narrative",
                        "Difficulty": 3
                    }
                ],
            "Rate": 1,   
            }
        },
        {
            "Volume":{
            "Definition": "Volume is a measure of the amount of space an object takes up. It's important for both practical and theoretical reasons. For example, if we're building a container to hold a certain amount of liquid, we need to know how to calculate the volume so we can make sure the container is big enough.",
            "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "Francisco is making an effort to drink more water, and has set a goal of 2 liters per day. He wants to know the volume of the water bottle he takes to school each day. The cylinder water bottle has base radius 4cm and height 20cm.\nWhat is the volume of Francisco's water bottle?",
                        "Answer": "To find the volume of Francisco's water bottle, we can use the formula for the volume of a cylinder, which is given by: V = \pi r^2 h, where: V is the volume of the cylinder, r is the radius of the base of the cylinder, and h is the height of the cylinder.\nSubstituting r = 4 and h = 20 into the formula, we obtain: V = \pi * 4^2 * 20 = 320\pi cm^3.",
                        "Type": "Narrative",
                        "Difficulty": 3
                    }
                ],
            "Rate": 1,   
            }
        }
    ],
    "Geometric transformations": [
        {
            "Translations":{
            "Definition": "A translation is a type of transformation that takes each point in a figure and slides it the same distance in the same direction.",
            "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "Draw the image of triangle ABC in the following figure under a translation by 2 units up:\nBEGIN PLOT:\nDraw('A', (1, 5))\nDraw('B', (4, 7))\nDraw('C', (3, 10))\nEND PLOT.",
                        "Answer": "The translation of point A with 2 units up is: (1, 7).\nThe translation of point B with 2 units up is: (4, 9).\nThe translation of point C with 2 units up is: (3, 12).\nConnecting 3 points, we can obtain the translation of triangle ABC up 2 units.",
                        "Type": "Narrative",
                        "Difficulty": 3
                    }
                ],
            "Rate": 1,   
            }
        },
        {
            "Rotations":{
            "Definition": "A rotation is a type of transformation that takes each point in a figure and rotates it a certain number of degrees around a given point. If the number of degrees are positive, the figure will rotate counter-clockwise. If the number of degrees are negative, the figure will rotate clockwise.",
            "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "Triangle A'B'C' is the image of triangle ABC under a rotation about the origin, (0,0) (in the following figure).\nBEGIN PLOT:\nDraw(`A'`, (-5, 2))\nDraw(`B'`, (-6, -3))\nDraw(`C'`, (-4, 1)\nDraw(`A`, (-3, -5))\nDraw(`B`, (3, -6)\nDraw(`C`, (-1, -4)).\nEND PLOT.\nDetermine the angle of rotation.",
                        "Answer": "Imagine a circle that passes through point C with a center at the origin.\nWe need to rotate point C through 1/4 of the circle clockwise to reach the image C', so the angle of rotation is 90 \degree clockwise.\nThe can check that the same rotation angle applies for points A and B.\nSo the rotation angle of the triangle is 90 \degree clockwise.",
                        "Type": "Narrative",
                        "Difficulty": 3
                    }
                ],
            "Rate": 1,   
            }
        },
        {
            "Reflections":{
            "Definition": "A reflection is a type of transformation that takes each point in a figure and reflects it over a line. The result is a new figure, called the image. The image is congruent to the original figure.",
            "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "Plot the image of quadrilateral ABCD under a reflection across the x-axis.\nBEGIN PLOT:\nDraw('A', (0, 1))\nDraw('B', (4, 1))\nDraw('C', (1, -5))\nDraw('D', (2, -1)).\nEND PLOT.",
                        "Answer": "\BEGIN PLOT:\nDraw(`A'`, (0, -1))\nDraw(`B'`, (4, -1))\nDraw(`C'`, (1, 5))\nDraw(`D'`, (2, 1)).\nEND PLOT.",
                        "Type": "Narrative",
                        "Difficulty": 3
                    }
                ],
            "Rate": 1,   
            }
        },
        {
            "Properties & definitions of transformations":{
            "Definition": "There are a few key vocabulary words and properties to keep in mind. For example, congruent shapes are exactly the same size and shape, while similar shapes have the same shape but may be different sizes.\nSome transformations — like reflections, rotations, and translations — preserve congruence. But dilations do not preserve congruence, since a dilation changes the size of a figure.",
            "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "Quadrilaterals EFGH and ABCD are congruent.\BEGIN PLOT:\nDraw('A', (14, 2))\nDraw('B', (14, -1))\nDraw('C', (11, -5))\nDraw('D', (11, -2))\nDraw('E', (2, 6))\nDraw('F', (5, 6))\nDraw('G', (9, 3))\nDraw('H', (6, 3))\nEND PLOT.\nDetermine a sequence of transformations that maps EFGH onto ABCD.",
                        "Answer": "First, we can do a rotation of 90 \degree clockwise through point H.\nThen a translation of 5 units along the x-axis, and a translation of -5 units along the y-axis would map the point H to point D.\nThis sequence of transformations also maps the quadrilateral EFGH into the quadrilateral ABCD.",
                        "Type": "Narrative",
                        "Difficulty": 3
                    }
                ],
            "Rate": 1,   
            }
        },
        {
            "Dilation":{
            "Definition": "A reflection flips a shape over a line, while a dilation makes a shape bigger or smaller by a certain factor.",
            "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "Draw the image of triangle ABC under a dilation whose center is A and scale factor is 4.\nBEGIN PLOT:\nDraw(`A`, (12, 3))\nDraw(`B`, (12, 1))\nDraw(`C`, (16, 1)).\nEND PLOT.",
                        "Answer": "The triangle DEF in the figure below is the image of the transformation.\nBEGIN PLOT:\nDraw(`D`, (12, 3))\nDraw(`E`, (12, -5))\nDraw(`F`, (28, -5))\END PLOt.",
                        "Type": "Narrative",
                        "Difficulty": 3
                    }
                ],
            "Rate": 1,   
            }
        }
    ],
    "Data and modeling": [
        {
            "Estimating lines of best fit":{
            "Definition": "A line of best fit is a way of summarizing the trend in a scatter plot. We draw the line so that it is as close as possible to as many of the points as possible. The line can help us make predictions about what might happen if we have new data points.",
            "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "The following list are 20 data points that represent the Physic score and Math score of 20 students. The list is: (1, 7), (6, 2), (11, 9), (16, 12), (21, 16), (27, 16), (32, 36), (37, 40), (42, 32), (47, 39), (53, 52), (58, 52), (63, 62), (68, 66), (73, 67), (79, 86), (84, 87), (89, 78), (94, 90), (100, 100). Which line of best fit would you suggest for these data?",
                        "Answer": "The data seems to follow a linear trend and could be estimated with a line of best fit.\nAs the slope seems to be close to 45 \degree, I will suggest the line x = y to estimate this data.",
                        "Type": "Narrative",
                        "Difficulty": 3
                    }
                ],
            "Rate": 1,   
            }
        },
        {
            "Two-way tables":{
            "Definition": "A two-way table shows the relationship between two categorical variables. It displays the counts or percentages of observations that fall into each combination of categories. The table is arranged into rows and columns, with each row representing one category of one variable and each column representing one category of the other variable.",
            "QA Queue": [
                    {
                        "Question": "Researchers surveyed recent graduates of two different universities about their income. The following two-way table displays data for the sample of graduates who responded to the survey. How many graduates in the sample came from University A?\nBEGIN TABLE\nIncome & University A & University B \nUnder $20,000 & 35 & 40 \n$20,000 to $39,999 & 90 & 63 \n$40,000 and over & 35 & 37 \nEND TABLE.",
                        "Answer": "To determine the number of graduates in the sample who came from University A, we need to sum up the values in the 'University A' column of the given two-way table.\nTotal graduates from University A = 35 + 90 + 35 = 160.\nTherefore, there were 160 graduates in the sample who came from University A.",
                        "Type": "Narrative",
                        "Difficulty": 3
                    }
                ],
            "Rate": 1,   
            }
        }
    ]
}